（忆往昔）
你当时是恶魔
You were a demon.
血印还在
You still have the mark.
那迟早会是麻烦
Sooner or later, that's gonna be an issue.
我的手下昨晚抓来一个离家出走的女孩
My men brought in a runaway last night.
毫无礼貌可言 我救了她都不知道谢我
She's got zero manners, didn't even thank me for saving her.
那些吸血鬼绑架了你 他们是怪物
Those vampires stole you. They're monsters.
你觉得他们其他人发现你走了之后
You think when the rest of them find out that you left.
他们会自认倒霉 不去多想吗
that they're just gonna shrug and cut their losses?
- 这是你家人吗 - 是
- This your family? - Yes.
他们怎么死的
How'd they die?
死得很惨
Horribly.
你想好要拿她怎么办吗
You know what to do with her?
乔迪 我做过一些坏事
Jody, I-I've done things.
你不用解释
You don't have to explain.
假如你需要 我就在这儿
If you want, I'm here.
汉斯姆警长在吗
Is sheriff Hanscum around?
抱歉 她这周后面几天都不在
Sorry. She's out for the rest of the week.
我已经减掉十磅了
I already lost 10 pounds!
一天吗
In… in one day?
我丈夫道格去年离开我了
My husband, Doug, left me last year.
道格就是个混球 你值得更好的
Doug's a dick. You deserve better.
（如今）
（明尼苏达 希宾）
[邪恶力量 第10季第8集]
你能撑过去的
You can get through this.
（欢迎来到明尼苏达 达科他 警长度假村）
你多大了
How old are you?
19.
去吃顿饱饭吧
Get yourself some lunch.
谢谢前来
Thanks a lot for coming.
谢谢 给你
Thanks. Here you go.
好好玩
Have fun!
来啊 欢迎
Yeah, welcome.
来吧
Come on.
你是
Sheriff…
乔迪·米尔斯警长 苏福尔斯
Sheriff Jody Mills, Sioux Falls.
好嘞
Okay.
我是唐娜·汉斯姆警长
I'm sheriff Donna Hanscum.
我在寂水工作 但我是本地人
I work out of Stillwater, but I grew up here,
如果你有什么疑问
so you have any questions…
比如哪家汉堡最好 油价最低
You know, best burgers, cheapest gas…
尽管问我
Just ask.
怎么了
What's wrong?
把微笑落在苏福尔斯了
Left your smile back in Sioux Falls?
是一个孩子
I left a kid back in Sioux Falls.
还有一堆工作
Plus a pile of work.
但既然镇长坚持让我来
But when the mayor insists you go…
你就没得选 可不是
You gotta go, yeah. I hear you.
来
Here.
- 吃个棒棒糖吧 - 不了 谢谢
- Have a sucker. - No, thank you.
好吧
O-okay.
唐娜
Donna.
道格
Doug.
你可真漂亮啊
Well, aren't you looking good, huh?
我减了6磅呢
I lost 6 pounds.
你已经成功四分之一了
You're 1/4 of the way there!
你…
Hey, you, uh…
能多给我几张饭票吗
You think you could toss me a couple extra meal vouchers?
反正你也不用了
I mean, since you won't be using them?
你总这么忠实 唐娜
You are true blue as ever, Donna, huh?
道格是我前夫
Doug and I used to be married.
懂了
Got it.
好好玩
Have fun.
我们没事吧
We good?
好极了
Aces.
我就喜欢一大早上闻羊皮纸的味儿
Yeah, I love the smell of parchment in the morning.
还剩多少传说啊
I mean, how much lore is even left?
我们完全查不到血印的事吗
We've got nothing on the mark?
是啊
Right?
按理说这群书呆子
You'd think these eggheads,
这些年囤积了这么多破烂
with all the crap they amassed over the years,
其中至少该有点真正重要的东西啊
would have actually collected something important.
看
Uh, here.
公狼/母狼 狼人变性的研究
"He-wolf/she-wolf: a study in werewolf transgenderism."
600页才第一卷
600 pages, volume 1.
但是真正重要的东西
But, uh, not something important, like…
比如人类历史上最古老的标记
I don't know… maybe the oldest symbol known to man.
就不值得研究一下了
That's not worth our time.
不够奇怪
It's not weird enough.
早上好
Uh, good morning.
打扰 请大家都就座
Uh, excuse me. If I could get you all seated, please.
早上好
Uh, good morning.
Morning.
我是伦·丘斯警长 来自希宾警局
I'm, uh, sheriff Len Cuse, uh, Hibbing P.D.
首先我想说 很荣幸
I'd like to say first off, uh, what an honor it is.
今年能在希宾招待大家
to have you all here in Hibbing this year.
我…
It, uh…
抱歉
Sorry.
Sorry. Uh…
抱歉了
Uh, sorry, folks.
我说到…
What was I, uh…
对了
Right. Right.
因为这是
S-seeing as how this is, uh,
- 我是第一次主持这种事 - 一看就是
- my first time hosting one of these things, - Obviously.
我想做些新的尝试
I thought I'd like to try something new.
结伴
Partners.
找一位工作地跟你相距
Uh, f-find… find an officer from 50 miles outside.
50英里的警官
of where you hail from.
组成本周末的队友
and be a team this weekend.
大家交交朋友吧
Go on, uh, a-and make a friend.
艾莉克斯 你没事的
Alex, I know you'll be okay.
你完全可以在我不在期间做到
You are totally capable of not throwing a kegger.
不办啤酒聚会 完全没问题
while I'm gone… totally, totally capable.
我对你的信心也令我惊讶
My faith in you astounds me, too.
我回头打给你
I'll call you later.
看来你没有队友呢
Looks like you didn't get a partner.
是啊
Looks like.
现在你有了
Well, you got one now.
（明尼苏达 达科他警长度假村 活动安排）
- 凯文 - 唐娜
- Hey, Kevin. - Hey, Donna.
都有什么啊
Okay, what did we get?
警察对冰雪 大雪下不停
"Cops VS. Winter: The Snow Must Go On."
组建警犬队 好吧
"Establishing a k-9 unit." Okay.
为暴乱做准备 何不试试
"Preparing for a riot… why not try it?"
何不呢
Why not?
好傻啊
I don't know.
- 唐娜 - 怎么了
- Hey, Donna. - Yeah?
- 听说尸体的事了吗 - 什么尸体
- Hear about the body? - What body?
是啊 什么尸体
Yeah, what body?
乔迪·米尔斯警长
Sheriff Jody Mills.
今早垃圾清理工在五金店后发现的
Trashmen found it behind the hardware store this morning.
被吃了
… eaten.
什么意思
Eaten how?
就剩个桃核了
Like nothing left but the peach pit, you know?
知道是什么东西干的吗
Any idea what did it?
验尸官说是林子里的野兽
Coroner's saying animals out of the woods…
山猫什么的
bobcats and whatnot.
怨不得刚刚丘斯警长那么慌乱呢
No wonder Sheriff Cuse was so out of sorts back there.
还要去处理这种烂摊子
Got this whole mess to deal with.
这一带经常发生这种袭击吗
Attacks like this common for the area?
当然不会
Heck no!
我住这儿的时候 动物才不会闹这种事
When I lived here, we kept our critters in check.
留下什么踪迹了吗 毛发什么的
Did it leave any tracks… you know, any hairs?
尸体上连个爪印都没有
Not even a claw mark on the body.
我就回来
I'll be right back.
好嘞 我给你留位子 乔迪
Okay. Yeah. Save ya a seat, Jods.
不会吧
No way.
乔迪 你怎么样啊
Jody. How's it going?
就那样呗
Uh, you know.
在希宾警长度假村逍遥快活呢
Having the time of my life at a sheriffs retreat in Hibbing.
听上去很棒啊
Wow. Sounds like a blast.
迪恩向你问好
Uh, Dean says hi.
你找到他了
You found him?
- 多谢告诉我啊 - 嗯
- Thanks for telling me! - Yeah.
是啊 抱歉了
Uh, right. Sorry about that.
他怎么样了
How's he doing?
挺好的
Good, good. Yeah, you know?
稍等一下
Uh, you know, hold on a sec.
我开免提
I'm gonna put you on speaker.
乔迪 艾莉克斯怎么样了
Hey, Jody. How's Alex holding up?
很好 已经当上拉拉队长了
Awesome. Already head of the cheerleading squad.
真的啊
Wow. Really?
才不是呢 萨姆 她躲在看台下抽大麻
No. Sam, she smokes grass under the bleachers.
但至少她没引诱男人去受死了
But at least she's not luring men to their deaths.
好吧
Right.
听我说 这或许不是你们查的那种案子
Listen, this may not be your kind of thing,
但今早这里发现了一具尸体
but a body was found here this morning,
而且是被严重撕咬过
and something had gone to chow town on it.
被撕喉了吗
Uh, was the throat ripped out?
更糟
Worse.
我听说吃得
I'm hearing that all the flesh.
只剩骨头了 有什么想法吗
had been eaten down to the bones. Any ideas?
肯定不是吸血鬼
Well, it's not a vampire.
我也不确定 乔迪 我想不到
Yeah, I-I don't know, Jody. I-I got nothing.
乔迪
Jody, um…
我们可以去看看
We could head that way.
完全不麻烦的
Wouldn't be any trouble at all.
没事 我自己能应付
Nah, it's okay. I can handle it.
如果我应付不了了 我会打给你们
I promise I'll call if it gets to be something I can't.
好吧
All right.
那好好在度假村玩
Well, uh, enjoy the retreat.
去你的 姓温的
Screw you, Winchester.
回头再聊
Talk soon.
如果还要我继续看这些玩意
I'm gonna swallow a bag of knives.
我就要吞刀了
if I got to keep looking at this stuff.
- 我们去… - 乔迪说她会应付 迪恩
- Let's… - Jody said she was on top of it, Dean.
好吧 我们走吧
All right. Let's take a drive.
我是乔迪·米尔斯警长
I'm sheriff Jody Mills.
我想看看今早被送来的尸体
I want to take a look at the body they brought in this morning.
好啊
Sure.
如果你是希宾警局的人就行
Soon as you become a member of the Hibbing police department.
我只是想帮忙
I'm just trying to help here.
我也只是不想丢了工作
And I'm just trying to not lose my job.
好久不见啊
Hey, stranger.
谢利 你好啊
Hiya, Shelly.
孩子们怎么样了
How are the kids?
那些小坏蛋 爱死他们了
Ah! Little jerks. Love them to death.
有事吗
Need something?
我就是想来看看被害人
Oh, I just came to check out the vic.
伦呢
Oh, where's Len at?
他在度假村忙得不可开交 不难想象
He's tied up with the retreat. Big surprise, right?
但我心想 住了一酒店的警长
But I figure what's the sense in havi"
还不帮帮忙 那还有什么意思
a hotel full of sheriffs if you can't help out?
该有人给你弄个天使的光环
Someone's got to get you a halo or something.
但是 她呢
But, um… what's her deal?
米尔斯警长啊
Oh, sheriff Mills?
她把礼貌都落在苏福尔斯了
Might say she left her manners back in Sioux Falls.
但她是跟我一起的
But she's with me.
怎么样 给我们看看吧
So, what do you say? Curtains up?
早餐憋住了 场面很吓人
Hold on to your breakfasts. This one's grisly.
天呐
Oofta.
全都吃掉了 这是肯定的
Ate the whole kit and caboodle. That's for darn sure.
你有卷尺吗
You got a measuring tape?
有
Yeah.
能给我看看他的私人物品吗
Can I see his personal effects?
那个小瘦子穿这么肥的裤子
That string bean wore these?
腰带呢
Where's the belt?
他没穿腰带
He wasn't wearing any.
这么大的裤子没腰带能撑住吗
These stayed up without a belt?
或许是被动物偷走了
Or… wild animals stole it.
乔迪 过来
Jodio. Check this out.
我从能拿小来复枪就开始打猎了
You know, I've been huntin' since I could hold a mini rifle.
什么样的咬伤都见过
Seen darn near every bite in the book,
但我却分辨不出咬伤他的是什么
but I couldn't tell ya what did the bitin' here.
我就担心这个
I was afraid of that.
什么意思
Meanin'?
没事 我也毫无头绪
Nothing. Got me stumped, too.
别去抽烟 豪伊
Don't go smoking, Howie.
看你的《超模》吧
Just watch your "Top Model."
伦 你好啊
Hiya, Len.
苏打水还对胃口吗
How's that seltzer treatin' ya?
你们有事吗
Something I can help you with?
昨晚的那起动物袭击听上去很严重啊
That animal attack last night sounded real bad, huh?
是啊
Yeah, sure was.
你觉得是什么动物干的
What kind of animal you thinkin' did it, now?
说不好
Uh, I don't know.
我们让动物管理局去解决了
We got animal control on it.
就这样吗
And that's it?
乔迪·米尔斯 苏福尔斯
Jody Mills, Sioux Falls.
丘斯警长
Sheriff Cuse.
出了点…
We have, uh…
问题
an issue with the…
抽奖的事
raffle.
好吧
Right.
失陪一下 我得去解决一下
Excuse me. I should go see to this. Uh…
好好玩 二位警长
Enjoy your night, sheriffs.
他也什么都不知道
He's got about as much I.D. as we do… squat.
或许他说得对
You know, maybe he's right.
让动物管理局去解决吧
Just let animal control take the lead.
推小车喽
Whoo! Push the cart!
以前跟他玩那个游戏的是我
I used to put the cans in his cart.
你真的想那种人吗
Are you really missing much?
老实说 唐娜 我才认识他
Honestly, Donna, I just met the guy, but…
但道格看上去像个混蛋
Doug seems like kind of a dick.
但他本来是我家的混蛋
But he was my dick.
我去睡了
I'm gonna go hit the can…
那里不会这么反胃
You know… where it's less gross.
好诶
Yeah!
- 别说出去 - 没出什么事吧
- Let's keep this to oursel… - Everything okay?
当然
Yeah, it's all good.
抽奖一切都好
All good with the raffle.
说真话吧
Can we get real, please?
好吧 你要真话
All right, um, you want real?
又死人了
Um… somebody else turned up dead.
看来又是动物袭击
Looks like another animal attack.
别说出去
Please, don't spread that.
我们不想搅了大家的兴致
We… we don't want to spoil everyone's good time.
- 或者太多人去管事 - 没错
- Or get too many cooks in the kitchen? - Exactly.
我和格拉姆警官要去打些电话
Now, uh, deputy Graham and I got to go make a few calls,
那么
Uh, so…
你好好玩吧 好吗
Try and have a good time, all right?
艾莉克斯
Alex…
别说了
Stop.
不
No! D…
为什么有鞭炮声
Why do I hear firecrackers?
喂
Hel…
看来你的生活也不那么完美喽
So, maybe your life's not all cupcakes, either.
我没说我完美啊
Never said it was.
又自己行动了吗
Flyin' the coop without me? Again?
- 不是 - 没事 我懂
- No. - No, I get it. I do.
「长点眼色吧 唐娜」 没事的
"Take a hint, Donna, " Right? It's okay.
又发生了一起动物袭击
There's been another animal attack.
不是吧 谁说的
Shut the front door. Says who?
我刚跟丘斯警长谈过
I just talked to Sheriff Cuse.
我正要去停尸房
I was on my way out of the morgue,
但现在估计关门了
but it's probably closed by now anyway, and…
明天再去吧
It'll wait till tomorrow.
需要我帮忙吗
Anything I can help with there?
除非你知道
Not unless you got any gems.
该怎么对付一个青春期女孩 我家那位…
on how to handle a teenage girl, 'cause mine is…
挺混蛋的
Kind of a dick?
她还有别的
She's got a whole lot more in there, too.
很不错的特质
Really good stuff.
我也17过
I was 17 once.
头发指天 脾气老大
Yeah, hair up to here, attitude up to here.
我怎么就无法触动她呢
Why can't I get through to her?
你那个年纪时会听劝吗
You let anybody through to you at that age?
乔·德莫皮德
Joey DeMoupied.
开摩托车
Drove a motorcycle.
闻起来…
Smelled like…
真不错
Yeah.
她会想通的
She'll come around.
你不就是吗
You did, right?
又死了人 混蛋前任
So, fresh corpse, jerk ex-husband,
不受控的少女
out-of-control teen.
要一起喝个大醉 看付费电视吗
Want to get blingo'd on my minibar and watch pay-per-view?
谢了
Thanks.
我还是去睡吧
I'm gonna crash.
今天好累
It's been a long day.
可不是
Don't I know it.
我说了我能应付的
I said I could handle it.
见到你也好高兴
Nice to see you, too.
我这就去停尸房 你们来吗
Okay, I'm headed to the morgue. You want in?
- 我们刚从那儿过来 - 怎么样
- Uh, we just came from there. - And?
第二位死者的肉也都被吃掉了
And flesh was eaten off the second vic, too.
少什么了吗
Anything missing?
他的钱包 怎么了
His wallet. Why?
因为我觉得第一个孩子的腰带丢了
Because I think a belt was missing off the first kid.
腰带
A belt? So…
怎么回事 怪物先吃后抢吗
what? We have monsters eating and then robbing people?
乔迪 你加糖吗
Jodio, you take sugar?
不 不用
No. No sugar.
好嘞
Okeydokes.
怎么回事
"Jodio"?
就是…
It's…
别问了
Don't ask.
等等
Wait a second.
那不是唐娜吗
Isn't that, uh, uh, Donna?
- 减肥水疗那个 - 没错
- Fat-spa Donna. - Right.
你们认识我的跟踪狂啊
You guys know my stalker?
她上次差点搞砸我们的案子
She nearly blew a case for us last time.
是啊 自从我到这儿
Yeah, I haven't been able to shake.
一直摆脱不掉她
that ray of sunshine since I got here.
她还挺能帮忙的
She's actually been pretty helpful,
但是想让她不发现这些
but, you know, it's just tough keeping her.
破事实在不容易
out of this nightmare stuff, you know?
嗯 你能牵制住她 让我们四处打探一下吗
Right. You mind distracting her while we poke around?
你们一跑来 我就变保姆了
You show up, and now I'm a babysitter?
她现在还没掺和进来
Look, she hasn't gotten mixed up with this crap yet.
我们努力别让她知道了
Let's just try to keep it that way.
好吧
Fine.
但如果她要给我看她的贴纸收藏 我就不干了
But if she tries to show me her sticker collection, I'm out.
菲利探员 克里斯探员
Agent Frehley? Agent Criss?
- 汉斯姆警长 - 我就觉得是你们
- Sheriff Hanscum. - I thought that was you.
太棒了 你们怎么来了
Well, ain't this a kick in the pants? What dragged you in?
我们不能多说
Uh, well, uh… we can't talk about it.
当然 明白
Oh. Yeah. I hear ya.
有什么要我帮忙的吗
Anything I can help with?
不用了
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. Uh, nothing.
其实 警长 我在想
Actually, sheriff, I was thinking.
咱们是不是去看看装备展览
you and I could go check out the gear expo.
那停尸房呢
What about the morgue?
你不是说了嘛
Well, you know, like you said,
动物管理局解决那事呢
animal control will handle that.
- 你不介意我就不介意 - 好极了
- Well, if it's cool with you, it's cool with me. - Great.
不过听说展品可很厉害呢
Did hear they're packing some pretty serious heat in there.
你们好 克里斯和菲利探员
Hey, there. Agents Criss and Frehley.
我们找警长
Looking for the sheriff.
希宾的警长
Of…Hibbing.
是我
That'd be me.
我们是来调查
Well, we're here investigating the attacks.
过去几晚的袭击
over the last couple nights.
不知道你进展如何了
Just wondering where you're at on that?
动物袭击吗
On the, uh… animal attacks?
- 对 - 等等
- Yeah. - Wait, wait, wait.
你们联调局没别的可做了吗
You telling me the FBI has got nothing better to do?
我们只是听命令而已
Well, we go where the boss tells us to.
来做什么 逮捕希宾的山猫吗
To what… arrest a bobcat from Hibbing?
有什么问题吗
Is there a problem?
没有 没问题
No. No, there's no problem.
你们不是第一个空手离开的联调局探员了
You ain't the first feds to roll through here and come up with nothing.
不过看你们努力很好玩
Sure is cute to watch you try, though.
伙计 联调局才不做「好玩」的事呢
Oh, pal, the FBI doesn't do cute.
丘斯警长 我们只是希望
Uh, Sheriff Cuse, we are just hoping.
有监控拍下了袭击事件
there might be some surveillance footage of the attacks.
或许交通摄像头什么的
Maybe a traffic camera caught something.
是啊 可惜 没有任何记录
Right. No. Sorry, I-I-I don't have a record of it.
说起来
Speaking of, uh…
你能替我照顾着展览的事吗 警官
Can you keep an eye on the expo for me, uh, deputy?
我得去动物管理局问问进展
I got to check in with the guys at animal control.
二位探员 认识你们很高兴
Agents, good to meet you.
自己拿点熊爪吃吧
Uh…help yourself to a bear claw.
警长在撒谎吗
Sheriff's lying?
混蛋警官似乎是这么想的
Deputy douche seems to think so.
好吧 我去试试破解警方服务器
All right. I'll go try and crack the police server.
或许监控拍到了什么
Maybe something showed up on surveillance.
嗯 我去试试那个警官
Yeah, maybe I'll go crack the deputy.
嗯 但这次是不是
Right, but this time, try to be.
别对你的幌子工作那么有保护欲
a little less defensive of your "pretend job."
这个局徽是有意义的
You know, this badge means something.
我在印刷店做的
I made it at kinko's.
是啊
Yes, you did.
感到骄傲吧
Be proud of that.
天呐
Son of a gun.
警官女士 看看这个
Uh, officer ladies, check this one out.
可以带去吃饭 去健身馆
You can take it to lunch, to the gym,
去做美甲
have your nails done.
她会一直陪着你们
She's always by your side.
这个呢
How about this puppy?
看情况了
Well, it depends.
这么大你没问题吗
Think you can handle a big one?
西格玛吧
Sigma, right?
10磅拉力 不错
10 pounds pull weight. Cute.
这就算大吗
Call this a big one?
希望你开的是保时捷
Hope you drive a porsche.
查兹
Chaz.
你要是想唬这姑娘
If you're trying to pull the wool over this one,
就大错特错了
You got the wrong girl.
汉斯姆警长是披着羊皮的猛狼呢
Sheriff Hanscum here is a wolf in sheepskin, right?
谢谢
Thank you.
狼的确很威猛
Wolves are majestic creatures.
但你的甜言蜜语留着给其他女人吧
But save your flattery for other female people.
古德希尔警长啊 不是的
Oh, sheriff Goodhill. No. No.
的确是那样
I mean, yeah.
但我们才认识嘛
But, you know, we just met.
- 铐友嘛 你懂的 - 什么
- Cufflinks… you know how it is. - Cuff what?
铐友 是一个警察的约会网站
Cufflinks! It's a dating site for cops.
你上那个网站吗 唐娜
You on it, Donna?
我 没有啊
Me? No.
我还没到那个时候
Not quite there yet.
你还在减肥呢
Oh, you still, uh, getting in date shape, huh? Huh?
应该说是
It's more like.
想先把我录的片子都看完
trying to get through the stuff on my dvr first.
老天啊
Oh, for the love of god.
你什么毛病啊
What is wrong with you?!
你就靠说女孩胖找自尊吗
You get off on fat-shaming chicks?
而且你一点不胖
You are so not fat, by the way.
你…
And you…
你就是个混蛋
You are just a douche.
好吧
Uh, okay.
那我…
I'll just, uh…
好吧
Okay, then.
你这是干什么 乔迪
What the h-e-double hockey sticks, Jody?
当面说我前夫是混蛋
Calling my ex a douche to his face?
反正看上去你也不打算这么做啊
It didn't look like you were gonna do it!
有什么意思 我们都离婚了
What would be the point? We're divorced!
你觉得我现在还能改变他吗
You really think I'm gonna change him now?
那他就永远可以欺负你吗
So he gets to treat you like a doormat forever? Is that it?
这样吧
How about this?
除非你也失去了丈夫
Till you've actually lost a husband,
你别来管我家的
you keep your mouth zipped about mine.
你丈夫出什么事了吗
Did something happen… to your husband?
我们都有各自的烦恼 不是吗
We all have our crosses to bear, right?
- 如果我说错话很抱歉 - 没事
- Hey, I'm sorry if I… - No.
很公平 是我先说了过分的话
That's fair. I certainly went there.
你想谈谈吗
You want to talk about it or…
现在不行
Not right now.
好吧
All right, then.
我去喘口气
I'm gonna go get some air.
探员
Agent.
你要来找小手铐
Are you looking for some teeny-weeny handcuffs.
给动物爪子戴吗
to slap on some paws?
我觉得我们有点误会
I think we got off on the wrong foot.
是啊
Right.
怎么说
How's that, exactly?
我和我搭档来这里进行的调查
Well, this investigation that my partner and I.
是件大事
are here on, it's… it's big.
我们需要本地警方的协助
And, uh, we're looking for some local help…
就是不会…
You know, someone who's not…
不敢跟华盛顿大人物打交道的人
not afraid to talk shop with the big boys back in D.C.
你对这有兴趣吗
Think that might be something you'd be interested in?
可能有
Might be.
我能做点什么呢
What can I do?
首先 我需要你对我完全坦诚
Well, first of all, I'm gonna need you to be totally straight with me.
有任何关于袭击的录像吗
Is there any footage of the attack …
什么都可以
anything?
昨天丘斯警长改了服务器的密码
Sheriff Cuse changed the password on the server yesterday.
上面有现场录像
It's got the live feed.
是第一起袭击现场街对面的
from the traffic camera across the street.
交通摄像头拍摄到的
from where that first vic got attacked.
我去查看那个录像时
When I went to go check the footage,
警长说他自己来就好
sheriff said he'd do it himself.
他有说原因吗
Did he say why?
但是你得知道 警长是个正直的人
But, you know, sheriff's a-a straight shooter.
他一定有自己的理由
I'm sure he had his reasons.
当然了
I'm sure he did.
好了 很感谢你的合作 警官
All right, well, I appreciate the cooperation, deputy,
我需要你的时候会来找你 好吗
and, uh, when I need you, I'll come find you, okay?
- 行 - 好
- All right. - All right.
狗屁「动物袭击」
Animal attack, my ass.
你看见丘斯警长了吗
You seen sheriff Cuse around?
展览之后就没看见了
Not since the Expo.
是啊 我也没有
Yeah, me neither.
你怎么样啊 孩子
How you doing, kiddo?
我吗
Me?
很棒啊 为什么这么问
Fantastic. Why?
传言说你几个月前出了点状况
Word 'round the campfire is you went off the res a couple months back.
是吗
That right?
你和萨姆一直在偷偷互通消息吗
You and Sam been passing notes during class?
我能应付
It's nothing I can't handle.
就这么随口一说
Just sayin'.
假如你想谈谈 我随时奉陪
I make a mean bowl of chowder if you ever need to talk.
谢谢
I appreciate that.
你找到什么线索了吗
You got something?
曾经有线索的
Uh, well, there was something.
我黑进了监控服务器
I hacked into the surveillance server,
但是文件已经被删除了
but the files had been deleted.
你不是说丘斯警长
I thought you said that sheriff Cuse.
是唯一能接触到那些文件的人吗
was the only one who had access to those files.
乔迪 我们能谈谈吗
Jody, can we talk a sec?
单独谈谈
Alone?
好的 我们到处转转去
Yeah, we'll go … we'll go look around.
好了 首先 我之前不应该插手的
Okay, first of all, back there, I was wrong to butt in.
我知道我伤害了你 我很抱歉
I know it hurt you, and I'm … I'm sorry.
什么
What?
哦 对了 「别甘受欺负」 没错
Oh. Yeah."Quit being a doormat." Yeah.
我知道了 乔迪 没事的
I hear ya, Jody. It's okay. We're okay.
只是…有些别的事
Only… there's something else.
我不太能理解
I can't quite wrap my head around.
你有想过世上有一些东西…
You ever think there are things out there …
一些…
things that…
不曾被警察记录在案的东西吗
don't end up on the police blotter?
你能详细说说吗
Can you give me some specifics?
可以 好的
Yeah. Okay.
我当时离得比较远
Well, I was … I was kinda far away,
所以可能是我看错了
so maybe I didn't see it right,
但是我觉得我看见了…
but what I think I saw…
牙齿
were teeth.
是丘斯警长
It was sheriff Cuse.
我看见他站在古德希尔警长的尸体旁边
I saw him standing over sheriff Goodhill's body,
而他的嘴里满是…
and his mouth was full of…
尖利的牙齿 就像是…
shark teeth, like some kind of…
怪物
Monster?
你觉得我疯了吧
You think I'm crazy.
完全不会
Not at all.
他看见你了吗
Did he see you?
没有
No.
我躲起来了 像个傻子一样
I hid … like a chump.
你真的相信我吗
You really believe me?
是的
Yeah.
那俩联调局的人也会相信你的
So will those guys from the FBI.
听你的
If you say so.
昨天 我看见丘斯把他的东西
Yesterday, I saw Cuse taking his stuff.
拿进了跟我隔了几间的房间
into a room down the hall from mine.
应该是…
Must have been…
304号
304.
我是菲利探员 请留言
This is Agent Frehley. Leave me a message.
萨姆 丘斯就是我们要找的人
Sam, Cuse is our guy.
唐娜说看到他进了304号房
Donna said she saw him check in to 304.
快回电
Hit me back.
现在怎么办
What now?
交给本地警方处理吗
Just let the locals handle it?
相信我
Oh, trust me…
这事绝不能让本地警方处理
The locals should not handle this.
看看这些防晒霜
Look at all this sunblock.
当他是在科帕卡巴纳海滩呢
You'd think he's at the Copacabana or somethin'.
我回头再解释
I'll explain later.
拿那玩意干什么
What the heck is that for?!
收到你的语音留言了
Got your voicemail.
- 她突然就抽出把刀 - 丘斯警长是吸血鬼
- She just pulled out a machete. - Sheriff Cuse is a vampire.
唐娜看到了他的牙齿
Donna saw his teeth.
什么鬼 吸血鬼
What the cuss?! A vampire?!
要跟她解释下吗
You want to give her the talk?
我靠
Heck.
我…靠
Just…heck.
没事了吧
We good?
等等 那之前在减肥水疗…
Wait. So, when we were at the weight-loss spa …
是怪物
Monsters.
吸走了你的脂肪
Sucking on your fat.
我们解决好了
We took care of them.
天啊
Aw, geez.
我就知道那么快减去10磅太不现实了
I knew losing 10 pounds that fast was too good to be true.
给
Here.
可能警长…吸血鬼就是去了这里
Maybe this is where sheriff…vampire went.
（424 跛子溪路）
不好猜啊
It could be anything.
查到什么
What do you got?
看来是镇外的一座旧农场
Looks like it's an old farm outside of town.
可能会有发现
Could be something.
这是我们仅有的线索
And it's the only lead we got.
我们
"We"?
不好意思 警长
All due respect, sheriff, but.
但吸血鬼可比你扔进监狱的
vampires are far more dangerous.
那些泛泛之辈要危险得多
than the johns you throw in jail.
你不能插手这事
You're gonna sit this one out.
去你的 迪恩
Stuff you, Dean!
不管你真名叫啥
Or whatever your real name is.
汉斯姆没问题
Hanscum's good.
- 乔迪 - 我说了她没问题
- Jody… - I said she's good.
好吧 那行 不过
Okay. All right. But,
你跟在后面
you're staying back.
我们带头 好吗
We're taking the lead, okay?
要挥就得使劲挥
If you're gonna swing, swing hard.
对付吸血鬼 得把头砍下来
With vamps, head's gotta roll.
明白
Got it.
快跑
Run!
你好啊 向日葵
Well, hi, there, sunflower.
这都是爱 小帅哥
It's all love, pretty boy.
你们都将融入我们体内
All of you will become all of us.
我们一点都不会浪费的
We won't waste one bit.
得了木法沙（出自电影《狮子王》） 少来生命循环的那一套
Okay, Mufasa, enough with the "Circle of life" Crap.
你是个吸血鬼
You're a vampire.
你是个败类 就这样
You're scum. End of story.
我可没心情
Yeah, I'm not in the mood.
等等 你们杀人还不够吗
Wait … it's not enough that you kill people.
还要抢人家的东西
You've got to rob them, too?
这叫搜刮
We scavenge.
我们不是喝两口就走
We don't sip and go.
我们会物尽其用
We use every part of the buffalo.
我居然还给过你午饭钱
And to think I gave you lunch money.
不过你正好赶上晚餐了
But you came in time for dinner.
斯塔尔 拜托 放他们走吧
Starr, please, let them go.
我已经帮了你们
I helped you out.
我把鲶鱼杀那男人的监控录像删了
I-I ditched that video o-of catfish killing that man.
我们不需要帮忙 伦
We didn't want favors, Len.
我们要的是你
We wanted you.
我现在能有什么用 我连人都不杀了
What use am I now? I don't even kill people.
我只喝袋装血
I-I'm on bagged blood.
你少来了
Uh, I beg your pardon?
我亲眼看到你露着吸血鬼的牙
I saw you with your vampire face.
站在古德希尔警长尸体边
standing over sheriff Goodhill.
不不 我发现了她
No, no, I-I-I found her. I …
我闻到了她的血的味道
I s-smelled her blood.
我控制不住我的
I-I couldn't help my …
我的尖牙
My fangs.
- 但我没有咬她 - 还真是个大英雄
- But I didn't bite. - Well, aren't you a hero.
吃人是你的天性
It's your nature to eat people.
不吸血的吸血鬼就像是 就像是
A vampire who doesn't feed is like a … like a…
吃素的老虎
Tiger eating salad.
我们不会停手的 伦
We're not gonna stop, Len.
我们会干掉你可爱的希宾镇上所有的人
We'll take down every person in your sweet, little Hibbing.
直到你回到我们中间来
till you come back to the nest.
你怎么回事 伦
So, what'd you do, Len?
打扰了他们的「火人节」狂欢吗
You, uh, break up Burning man?
伍德斯托克狂欢更贴切
More like Woodstock.
我爸爸把我赶出了家门 是伦在路边发现了我
Len found me crying on the curb after my daddy kicked me out.
我上了伦的车
I got in Len's van,
接下来 就是「血池肉林」了
and the rest is wavy gravy.
那么伦就是你的杀人导师了 就像查理·曼森（邪教组织的领袖）
So, what … Len's like your Charlie Manson?
查理才比不上伦呢
Charlie couldn't hold a candle to Len.
他把一切都教给了我们
He taught us everything.
肯定都是些神神叨叨的东西吧
Yeah, I'm sure it was all kombucha and kumbaya.
他教会了我们释放天性
Liberating is what it was.
结果有一天 伦突然不见了
And then, one day, poof! Len's gone.
直到他的照片出现在了报纸上 太蠢了
Till he landed his photo in the paper. Stupid.
他开了一家警察度假村
For running a police retreat, of all things.
你不仅改过自新了
You didn't just go straight.
居然还成了一个该死的警察
You became a damn cop.
这也太过了 伙计
Now, that is wild, man.
你感受到野性了吗 伦
Are you feeling dirty, Len?
我们马上要大开杀戒了
'cause we're about to have ourselves a bloodbath.
你不想知道我为什么离开吗
Don't you want to know why I left?
我知道为什么
I already know why.
你觉得无聊了
You got boring.
我有了良知
I got a conscience.
猎物祈求我们饶他们一命
Prey that begged for their lives …
即使像我教你们的那样
I-it was like even if I used every part,
不浪费一点
like I taught you,
这样也还是错的
I mean, it's still wrong.
所以你离开了
So you walked away.
我想保护人类
I tried to protect people.
在我残食了他们那么多年后
After so many years of…gutting them.
这就是我来这里的原因
That's why I'm here.
我加入你们的吸血大军
I'll join your bloody caravan…
只要你们不杀了这些人
If it means you won't kill these people.
我们不会杀任何人
We aren't killing anyone.
你来杀
You are.
你不必这么做的
You don't have to do this.
见鬼去吧
Kiss my ass.
我们爱你 兄弟
We love you, brother.
但我们已经不认识你了
But we don't know who you are anymore.
别说我们没努力过
Can't say we didn't try.
这下逍遥了 小姑娘
Hakuna matata, lady.
这才像话呢
Now, that's what I'm talking about.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
就是有点想吐 除此之外很好
Other than feeling like I want to hurl, sure.
我刚刚 砍下了 一个吸血鬼的脑袋
I just…chopped off… A vampire's head.
- 你很厉害呢 - 谢谢
- You were great at that. - Thanks.
你没事吧
You good?
没事
Yeah.
这是我回来以后第一次
Yeah, you know, for the first time I've been back,
没感觉受到血印的驱使
I didn't feel like the mark was pushing me.
第一次
First time?
知道有这些东西的存在
Knowing that these things are out there.
让世界看起来 我说不好
makes the world seem … I don't know …
更大了
Bigger…
更黑暗了
Darker.
刚刚杀掉那些吸血鬼时 我感觉…
All I know is, back there, killing those vamps…
又变回自己了
I felt like me again.
那么 这是
All right. So, that's…
好事 对吗
good, right?
是啊
Yeah.
如果你想了解怎么对付这些怪物
You know, if you want any pointers on how to fight this crazy crap,
我很乐意给你讲讲 他们的克星什么的
I'm willing to fill you in … you know, what kills what.
那太好了
I'd like that.
那好
Okay.
那就这样吧
Well, let's go with that.